
--- READING Homework Assignment 2025-2026.pdf ---

Error reading e:/IACV/HOMEWORK 2025-2026-20251224/Homework Assignment 2025-2026.pdf: 'charmap' codec can't encode characters in position 351-352: character maps to <undefined>

--- READING Homework Delivery Instructions 2025-26.pdf ---

HOMEWORK DELIVERY: 
Submit a compressed file (or separate files within a personal directory) containing the items listed 
below to the Image Analysis and Computer Vision page on the WeBeep Platform, (Homework 
2025-2026 page, Delivery folder) by Tuesday, January 20, 2026, 23 h 59, Milano local time. Also, 
send a notification via e-mail to vincenzo.caglioti@polimi.it within January 21, 2026, 09 h 00, 
Milano local time. The submission must include: 
- the used input image 
- the above image with extracted features (edges, corners, lines) 
- computed results (useful vanishing points, vanishing line, rectification 
mapping, computed shape and size of the diagona arcs, coordinates of 
required points, calibration parameters, camera pose relative to the object, 
required plots) 
- well written report including problem formulation, solutions to the theoretical 
questions, well-explained solution approach for the various steps, experimental results 
and their analysis 
- commented Matlab code. 
 
 
ATTENTION: Submission of multiple files in the Delivery folder is NOT ALLOWED: 
Please submit either a single compressed file or construct your own directory. 
 
REMEMBER: Please notify the teacher about your submission by 
sending an e-mail to vincenzo.caglioti@polimi.it within january 21, 
2026, 09 h 00. 
 
 
IMPORTANT: please ATTACH the HOMEWORK REPORT to your notification 
mail (ONLY the report should be attached). 
 
VERY IMPORTANT: the Homework is INDIVIDUAL! Cooperation is 
not allowed, and Homeworks made in COOPERATION will not be 
considered. 

--- READING IACV 2025 - I - About Homework and Projects.pdf ---

Homework
ONLY USE SPECIFIED INFORMATION !
diagonal arcs are 
parallel but they
are not conics
Some project topics
a partial list
Analysis of motion-blurred images


Visual analysis of moving vehicles
P V
l
Q
Find USEFUL symmetric points from light contours
1. Bitangents 2. Points colinear to vanishing point
Error reading e:/IACV/LECTURE SLIDES 2025-20251224/IACV 2025 - I - About Homework and Projects.pdf: 'charmap' codec can't encode character '\uf0e0' in position 19: character maps to <undefined>
